<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-07-19T20:04:29-04:00</updated><id>http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//</id><title>Code and Cappuccinos</title><subtitle>A blog with an author who loves to code, and drink cappuccinos.</subtitle><entry><title>Really Awesome and Easy Healthier Brownies</title><link href="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2017/06/14/really-awesome-and-easy-healthier-brownies/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Really Awesome and Easy Healthier Brownies" /><published>2017-06-14T09:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-06-14T09:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2017/06/14/really-awesome-and-easy-healthier-brownies</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2017/06/14/really-awesome-and-easy-healthier-brownies/">&lt;p&gt;Recipe first, ramble later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/2 cup peanut flour&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/2 cup vanilla Vega One or any other protein powder&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3-5 Tbsp cacao/cocoa powder&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;~2Tbsp flour of choice (I used oat flour)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;~6 packets of stevia powder (6 grams) (you can add more or less if you want to adjust the sweetness)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 tsp baking powder&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/2 Tsp salt&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 cup milk or milk subsitute of choice (or even water if you don't have anything)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 tsp vanilla extract&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 tsp honey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 tsp warmed coconut oil or &quot;manna&quot; (blended coconut - soooo good)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Steps:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Preheat oven to 350F.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Combine the dry ingredients first, making sure that you get and many of the clumps out of the peanut flour as you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Make a hole in the center (shove everything off to the sides) and pour in your 1 cup of milk, then the vanilla, honey, and coconut oil&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. Mix the wet incredients in until you get a consitency that's not as wet as browney batter but not as dry as a paste. Somewhere in between is perfect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5. Put parchment paper down in a 9x9 inch pan (or grease the pan) and squish your mixture into it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6. Put it in the oven for 20-25 minutes then let it cool until you cant wait any longer!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nononsensenutritionist.com/recipes/snacksandsweets/peanut-flour-pb2-protein-bars/&quot;&gt;Adapted from this recipe by No Nonsense Nutritionist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Ramble&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I've started working out more because my job has me sitting down all day and I've been noticing an increase in cellulite on my legs. (No thanks!) In an effort to try and save money on one of my favourite go to snacks -protien bars I came across the recipe linked above. I decided to try it out but in true Brittny-like fashion I improvised a bit nd they turned out more like brownies than anything else! If you love chocolate and need a post workout pick me up (or you just crave chocolate) give this recipe a go! I'm not a professional baker or anything but it tasted really good to me :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Here are some pics to help you out!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/20170611_160105.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What consistancy my batter was - tastes better than it looks at this point ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/20170611_160119.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The products I used&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Brittny Lapierre</name></author><summary>Recipe first, ramble later.</summary></entry><entry><title>Manic Panic Fuschia Shock Review</title><link href="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/11/26/manic-panic-fuschia-shock-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Manic Panic Fuschia Shock Review" /><published>2016-11-26T16:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-11-26T16:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/11/26/manic-panic-fuschia-shock-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/11/26/manic-panic-fuschia-shock-review/">&lt;p&gt;It's winter now and I'm experimenting with berry-purple-pink colours!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mpfs.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I dyed my hair with Joico's Rose semi-permanent dye for Halloween. Oh god was that stuff ever horrible. The colour was a pale pink which was good since that's what I wanted but it washed out super fast leaving my hair peach coloured, which I don't mind. The main problem with the dye is that for some reason they decided to put glitter in it. GLITTER!! -_- Why would they do that? They were large enough flakes that it wouldn't just make my hair look shiny either. Man, there was glitter everywhere for days after I dyed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways once that faded out I was left with yellow blonde-peach hair. I had some leftover Manic Panic in the colour Fuschia Shock from when I dyed my hair last winter so I decided to use it. I didn't have much left so I mixed it with conditioner. The result was a really vibrant (like a highlighter) dark pink, it was really nice!  It was lighter than I remembered from last year though, the reason for that was because I mixed it with conditioner. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After about two weeks it started to fade and got kind of dull so I bought another jar and put it straight on my hair. This brand of dye, no matter the colour but especially for the pinks and reds, leaks everywhere for the first week or so when you don't mix it with conditioner! My bathtub gets temporarily stained from it, and usually, my neck gets a little tinted even when I'm trying to be careful. T.T The colour payoff is amazing though if you're looking for seriously vivid colour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mpfsb.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Manic panic definitely comes off onto your hands in the shower! Either wash your hands often or wear gloves to prevent this from happening. I also flip my hair up over my forehead and keep my head down while in the shower so the dye doesn't run down my back and stain it. Also, I usually squeeze most of the water out of my hair before I leave the bathtub, and then immediately cover my hair with an old t-shirt I don't care about. This prevents the dye from dripping all over the place in my house or staining my skin. You only have to do this for the first week or two, though!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you're looking for a semi-permanent dye that doesn't last quite so long as Manic Panic but leaks less and is less hassle, check out the Ion Colour Brilliance line. I've used their fuschia colour, and an awesome colour called Rose Quartz, and both times I didn't have to worry too much about the dye staining my nail or hands in the shower.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Brittny Lapierre</name></author><summary>It's winter now and I'm experimenting with berry-purple-pink colours!</summary></entry><entry><title>My Top 6 Favourite Anime, Cartoons, and Animations!</title><link href="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/11/16/my-top-6-favourite-anime-cartoons-and-animations/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Top 6 Favourite Anime, Cartoons, and Animations!" /><published>2016-11-16T08:30:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-11-16T08:30:00-05:00</updated><id>http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/11/16/my-top-6-favourite-anime-cartoons-and-animations</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/11/16/my-top-6-favourite-anime-cartoons-and-animations/">&lt;h3&gt;1) Ouran Highschool Host Club&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ouranhshc.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's over the top and weird and I love it! It's a not-so subtle paradoy of typical anime and manga tropes and it's just so, so perfect. I've probably re-watched the series at least 5 times and read the manga over twice, which says a lot because I don't normally read non-fiction!

It's about a poor girl who doesn't care about appearances at all that is on scholarship to this fancy private school for rich kids. She gets mistaken for a boy at first and somehow becomes involved with a hostclub after trying to find a queit place to study. Throughout the episodes we learn more about the eccentric other hostclub members. One after another they learn that she is infact a girl, and they need to keep that fact secret from the rest of the school! It's an awesome melodromatic-comedy-romance. 

If you also love the anime, definitely read the books, or at least the last few chapters! I always seem to go for the underdog so I was rooting for Hikaru.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;2) Avatar: The Last Airbender&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/airbender.jpg&quot; /&gt;
Guysssss...&lt;br /&gt;
Guysssssssssss...&lt;br /&gt;
BENDING IS SOO COOL!&lt;br /&gt;
I was so late in the game to watch this series but man am I ever glad I did! I just finished it with Steven a couple weeks ago. As a 21 year old, it seemed a little kiddish at first but it soons grows on you and gets more deep and real. It's about courage, oppression, duty, family, friendship, forgivingness, identity, and training... just about everything. The characters are relatable, and inspirational and it's full of strong female role models too! The cartoon shows the journey of Aang, the last of the Air Bending Nation. Aang is also the Avatar, the one bender of every generation that can master all four elements, earth, water, air, and fire. The airbenders were wiped out by the Fire Nation during their conquest. Aang has to become a master of all of the elements and defeat the Fire Lord and restore balance to the world with the help of his friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;3) Avatar: The Legend of Korra&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/korra.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bolin and Pabu though, am I right?&lt;br /&gt;
This series is awesome! It tells the story of the avatar who comes after Aang, Korra of the Southern Waterbending Tribe She's a super strong (and strong willed) young woman who grows and overcomes so much during the series. This series is full of decendant's of characters in the first Avatar series and we even get to see Katara, Toph, and Zuko! Just like in the Last Airbender, the Avatar needs the support of her friends to overcome her obstacles. This series is darker than the last one, which makes it perfect for people who've grown up a little since the last series. You can enjoy this show without watching the last series but you'll miss out on a lot of nods to the old series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;4) Bleach&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/bleachcharacters.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This anime is overflowing with seriously bad ass characters, being serious and dark(ish?) sometimes but also hilarious! I love an anime that shows how hard work and friendship go a long way. This story is about Ichigo, a substitute shinigami! A shinigami cleanses souls which have turned into hallows (these big demon ghosty monster things). Each shinigami belongs to a squadrant of the Soul Society's Shinigami. Each squadrant is headed by a captain (yay Toshiro), and they are all soo cool. The show doesn't give you all of the information about each character at first, instead you learn their general personality and power level and it eases you into learning more and more about them. Like in almost every cartoon/anime/animation that I like Ichigo is supported by his friends, Orihime, Chad, and Uryu. The 'Agent of the Shinigami' to the 'Arrancar' arcs (not including the filler Bount arc, although I did watch it) are my favourite of the different story arcs but I won't complain seeing more and more bleach! It's full of lovable and inspiring characters. Oh and that music that plays when stuff's about to get real... if you've watched it you know what im talking about. :')&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;5) Earth's Mightiest Heroes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/emh.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Features like every Marvel superhero and villain ever! Well, not really but they feature tonnnsss of different heros and villians. This series shows the Avengers but it doesn't perfectly align with the movies, it features Avengers who aren't in the movies (or weren't until recently) like Ant Man, The Wasp, and The Black Panther. There's a newer cartoon which does called Avengers Assemble but I prefer this one. I love this show because it's funny and gives you more detail about the members of the Avengers and other Marvel characters. The storyline's also pretty solid! Also, Hawkeye's original outfit. XD&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;6) RWBY&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/rwby.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is another series that grew on me, slower than Airbender but still pretty quickly. At first I found it the animation pretty but the dialogue was kind of cheesy. The story gets more complex and the writing gets better so keep watching it! It's about a girl called Ruby who is attending Beacon Academy to become a Huntress who fights off monsters with a sick scythe! She has a group of friends named Weiss, Blake, and Yang Xiao who are also members of her team, named RWBY after their names, at the academy. If you like fairy tales, supernatural stuff, and cool animation this is a good series for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--h3&gt;7. Full Metal Alchemist&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;8. Grave of Fireflies&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;9. Spirited Away&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;10. My Neighbor Totoro&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;11. Black Butler&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;12. Code Geass&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;13. Deadman Wonderland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;14. The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;15. Angel Beats&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;16. Akb0048&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;17. Howl's Moving Castle&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;19. Stiens;Gate&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;20. Fate/Stay Night&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;21. Blue Exorcist&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;22. Chi's Sweet Home&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;23. Cardcaptor Sakura&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;h3&gt;24. School Rumble&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;25. Inu Yasha&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;26. K-on!&lt;/h3--&gt;</content><author><name>Brittny Lapierre</name></author><summary>1) Ouran Highschool Host Club

It's over the top and weird and I love it! It's a not-so subtle paradoy of typical anime and manga tropes and it's just so, so perfect. I've probably re-watched the series at least 5 times and read the manga over twice, which says a lot because I don't normally read non-fiction!</summary></entry><entry><title>I Made a Cute Logo for the Blog!</title><link href="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/11/14/i-made-a-cute-logo-for-the-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Made a Cute Logo for the Blog!" /><published>2016-11-14T07:30:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-11-14T07:30:00-05:00</updated><id>http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/11/14/i-made-a-cute-logo-for-the-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/11/14/i-made-a-cute-logo-for-the-blog/">&lt;h3&gt;Adobe Illustrator Makes Logo Making so Easy!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm super happy with my first logo design ever. It's simple but that's exactly why I like it. In case it's not too obvious, it's a cappuccino and the double ampersand (&amp;amp;&amp;amp;) which is used in lots of programming languages as the logical and operator!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/icon.png&quot; style=&quot;display: inline-block;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Brittny Lapierre</name></author><summary>Adobe Illustrator Makes Logo Making so Easy!
I'm super happy with my first logo design ever. It's simple but that's exactly why I like it. In case it's not too obvious, it's a cappuccino and the double ampersand (&amp;amp;&amp;amp;) which is used in lots of programming languages as the logical and operator!</summary></entry><entry><title>I’m Not Very Good at This…</title><link href="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/10/27/not-good/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I'm Not Very Good at This..." /><published>2016-10-26T22:30:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-10-26T22:30:00-04:00</updated><id>http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/10/27/not-good</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.codeandcappuccinos.com//2016/10/27/not-good/">&lt;h3&gt;Welcome to my online journal.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or blog as they call it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The concept of me writing down my thoughts and publishing them online is very new and strange to me. I feel as time goes by and I become more comfortable, my posts will become better and better. For now though, you're stuck with newbie Brittny.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Brittny Lapierre</name></author><summary>Welcome to my online journal.
Or blog as they call it.
The concept of me writing down my thoughts and publishing them online is very new and strange to me. I feel as time goes by and I become more comfortable, my posts will become better and better. For now though, you're stuck with newbie Brittny.</summary></entry></feed>
